I: What’s your idea of happiness?
S: That’s a difficult question.
Um, my idea of happiness is probably relaxing with friends in my home,
listening to nice music, with lovely food for everyone.
I: What foreign languages do you speak?
T: I speak French.
I: How well do you speak it?
T: Quite well. Not fluently, but well enough to get around.
I: If you have a problem, who do you ask for advice, friends or family?
K: When I have a problem, I usually ask close friends for advice.
I: Why?
K: My parents are a lot older than me,
so their advice is really great for certain things,
but most of the things I’m going through right now, my friends are pretty good.
I: What advice would you give someone who can’t sleep at night?
J: If someone couldn’t sleep at night,
I’d usually advise them to do something like meditation,
so some kind of breathing exercise which would calm them down, um,
and also just to be in an environment where they feel comfortable and safe I guess,
rather than in an environment that stresses them out,
maybe keep their phone out of the bedroom, or something like that.
I: Do you think the British are bad at learning languages?
A: I think we do tend to be rather bad at learning languages.
I: Why?
A: I think we can be a bit lazy, because everybody else speaks English.